{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"8709/98",
			"answer":"8709/98",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3114/68",
			"answer":"3114/68",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6827/89",
			"answer":"6827/89",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1486/98",
			"answer":"1486/98",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8108/84",
			"answer":"8108/84",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.9734/31",
			"answer":"0.9734/31",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"28.98/0.042",
			"answer":"28.98/0.042",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"806.6/0.74",
			"answer":"806.6/0.74",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.3432/0.66",
			"answer":"0.3432/0.66",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"973.4/31",
			"answer":"973.4/31",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}